toprooms.com 2015-06-18

# Privacy - Toprooms.Com

1\. Your consent

By using our Website and providing personal details, including where you use the Website to search or book accommodation, you consent to the collection, use and retention of your personal information for our legitimate business purposes as explained and set out in this Privacy Policy.

2\. Collection, use & retention of information

We collect, use and retain information about you to the extent only that is reasonably required to conduct our business effectively.  
The information collected varies depending on the service you request from us. For example, when you use the Website to book accommodation, we may collect personal details such as your name, address, accommodation details, credit/debit card number and expiry date, billing details and telephone numbers. This information may be collected from third parties including the third party accommodation provider who you access via our Website and who you place your booking with, or other people who collect information on our behalf such as regional and local tourism agencies. We also collect information directly from you when you speak to us over the telephone or send us correspondence or rate and comment on the accommodation. Finally, we undertake market research, or have third parties undertake it on our behalf and collect information in that way.  
We use information to complete transactions on your behalf and to ensure that we can efficiently manage and track transactions that are processed through our system. Your credit/debit card details are only used to process the transaction you have requested and are not stored or used in any other way by us. We also use information to monitor our system efficiency and use, and to test and developenhancements and changes to the way we do business.  
The information that we collect may be transferred to and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA) and may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers or contractors, to process or manage transactions using our system.  
The Website contains links to other sites including web pages of third party accommodation providers with whom you can book accommodation. Although this Privacy Policy applies to information about you that is provided to us by those third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy policies of those other sites and will not be liable for those policies.

3\. Protection of information

We maintain appropriate security standards and procedures in relation to the collection, use and retention of your information in order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure. Should you contact us, our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we are able to disclose any information to you.

Back to top

4\. Disclosure to third parties

Information is shared with our groupcompanies, contractors, data processing companies including operators of global distribution systems and payment clearing houses, bank and professional advisers. We share only the information necessary to deliver any supply of products and/or services by us to you or in order to ensure the successful completion of a transaction processed through our system or for related purposes. We may also disclose your information when necessary to protect against fraud or any other crime (usually by providing such information to a reputable information reporting organisation) or in the event that we sell our business then to the purchaser of that business.  
We may in addition from time to time share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with third parties for business purposes, for example we may tell our business partners including regional tourism agencies and commercial distributors the number of customers in certain demographic groups who purchased accommodation using our system. This does not involve the disclosure of any personal information which can identify any particular customer in any way.  
Finally, we may disclose your personal information at any time where necessary to comply with any legal obligation or requirement, such as to comply with an order of the court.

Back to top

5\. Online guest reviews

After your stay in accommodation booked through us, we may email you a questionnaire asking you to rate and comment on your stay. The purpose of customer reviews is to helpother customers understand what a particular accommodation is like, to give feedback to the property (so that they can improve) and to helpus understand more about your stay and improve our services.  
If you complete and submit the questionnaire your review of the accommodation may be automatically posted onto our booking websites, the website of the property and related websites. You should therefore be careful about what you say (e.g. as regards disclosing your personal data) as it may enter the public domain and be available for anyone to read. The property you review may be given an opportunity to respond to the review which you have submitted and their response may also automatically enter the public domain alongside yours.  
We may also use the information you submit to correspond with you about a review which you have submitted.

Back to top

6\. Employee access to information

Your information is disclosed to our employees, agents and representatives on "a need to know" basis and we confirm that all such persons understand the importance of client confidentiality and privacy.

Back to top

7\. Share facility

If you use the Share facility on our site and give us details of another person (e.g. their name and email address), you should make sure that the other person is content to receive the information. We will only use their data for the purpose of the Sharing facility.

Back to top

8\. Updating, maintenance and accuracy of your information

We do our best to ensure that all information held relating to you is kept up-to-date, accurate and complete.  
Data populated by you (including your personal details entered in any fields) is your sole responsibility and any changes to any aspect of your personal data should be updated directly by you.  
If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us on [enquiries@toprooms.com](mailto:enquiries@toprooms.com "email for information") and we will endeavour to respond as soon as possible. All of our processes and data storage methods have been approved by the Information Commissioner’s Office ( [www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk](http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/ "Information Commissioner") ) and our registration number is Z1431368.

Back to top

9\. Cookies and other non-personal information

When you visit the website, we may automatically collect non-personal information about you, such as the type of internet browser you use, the website from which you have come to the website and your Ipaddress (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognised by our web server. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on the website and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use.  
The website uses cookies to store certain information. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you register or subscribe at our website that enable our server to recognize or "remember" who you are each time you return. We may make limited use of cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. For instance they may be used to retain your personal preferences, hold session information or save your password so it doesn't have to be re-entered each time you login. You can erase or block cookies from your computer if you want to (your helpscreen or manual should tell you how to do this), but certain services may not work correctly or at all if you set your browser not to accept cookies.  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, please visit the Network Advertising website.

Back to top

10\. Complaints procedure

If you wish to make a complaint about eviivo, our services or any associated matter, you may contact us by telephone, email, letter or fax. We do not require complaints to be in writing. Wherever possible, complaints will be dealt with promptly, and you will receive a response within14 working days.  
If you are dissatisfied with the outcome of your complaint, you may choose to escalate the complaint internally by contacting our Customer Support Manager, [enquiries@toprooms.com](mailto:enquiries@toprooms.com "email for information"). A response to an escalated complaint will also be made within 7 working days.

Back to top

11\. Company details

**eviivo Limited**  
The Grimaldi Building, 154 Pentonville Road, London N1 9JE  
**E-mail:** enquiries@eviivo.com  
**Telephone:** +44 (0)844 880 3000  
**Fax:** +44 (0)844 880 3000

Back to top
